https://www.thedieselpage.com/privacy.htm

TheDieselPage.com Privacy Statement
Updated: January 3, 2020
TheDieselPage.com has been online and operating a commercial editorial service since 1996.
We respect your privacy. This Privacy Statement will explain how and why we collect certain information both online and offline, and how we use that information. This statement also explains how you can prevent collection of certain information about yourself if you choose to do so. Please take a few moments to read our Privacy Statement. This statement applies to information we collect from visitors to the TheDieselPage.com web site, as well as information we collect or have access to when hosting a bulletin board forum, a mailing list and subscribing member database.
Right to Change Policy:
TheDieselPage.com will continue to enhance the content and services provided to its members and web site visitors. This Privacy Statement will also evolve to match the content and services we make available, and we reserve the right to change this statement to match the content and services we provide. If we make any substantive change to this statement, the date at the top of this statement will reflect the effective date of that change. When you visit our site or use our content and services, we encourage you to check the date of this Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of any updates.
However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, TheDieselPage.com will not collect or maintain your private or personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to legal claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, its employees, subscribing members, customers, or the public.
Contact for Privacy Inquiries:
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or have any other questions about privacy here on the TheDieselPage.com web site, please contact: Via Postal Service Mail:
Via E-Mail: Turbo@TheDieselPage.com
Types of Information We Collect:
Generally, you are free to browse the visitor areas of TheDieselPage.com web site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the TheDieselPage.com site unless you register for the TheDieselPage.com forum, submit the membership application, complete one of our surveys, or otherwise agree to share such information with us. As part of such processes, you have the opportunity to decline further notifications from us regarding special offers and/or information from TheDieselPage.com. Types of information collected by the TheDieselPage.com web site are described below in more detail.
TheDieselPage.com Bulletin Board Registration:
Bulletin Board registration is required for users who wish to interactively participate in the TheDieselPage.com bulletin board and mailing list. In order to register, you must provide us with a username (which does not have to be your real name), password and a valid e-mail address. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings, and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. As currently configured, your e-mail address will remain hidden from other users when registering for and using TheDieselPage.com's bulletin board forum.
However, accessing all areas of our free bulletin board forum or accessing the member/subscriber areas of the web site requires registration.
For your own protection, we recommend that you select a unique login name and password for our Bulletin Board forum. Using the same code set for multiple Internet venues can put you at risk, especially if that code set is also used to access an email account or online financial service.
When you register for the forum, you have the option of providing additional information, such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This optional information is viewable by other TheDieselPage.com users, and helps to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank.
Your forum registration will be processed without this additional information.
Our Bulletin Board administrators and moderators cannot review all messages posted and are not responsible for the content of any of messages posted by others. If you feel a message posted by another is improper, please make an administrator or moderator aware of your concern. The Bulletin Board administrators and moderators reserve the right to delete or edit any posted message for any reason whatsoever if that message violates our Bulletin Board forum guidelines or is otherwise deemed inappropriate. You are an invited guest into our bulletin board forum home.
It is important for you to know that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a message posted on our or any Bulletin Board or online classified ad, that this information is available to anyone who has access to TheDieselPage.com web site,
or bulletin board forum, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For your own protection, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posted message to this or any other online discussion group.
Persons UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE:
Persons UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE are not allowed to participate in the TheDieselPage.com forum or mailing list, or to provide any personal information on our site unless supervised by a parent or legal guardian. This web site is intended for a general audience, which excludes adult oriented language and/or content. However, due to the real-time nature of user posts to the bulletin board and mailing list, offensive material could make its way into a forum topic before we have an opportunity to remove it.
Cookies:
TheDieselPage.com web site and bulletin board use browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our web site and other online services. These cookies are small segments of code that our web server sends to your browser, which it can then store on your hard drive. If your browser is set to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your web browser has visited previously and has used our web site.
These cookies enable us to recognize you when you access the member/subscriber areas of the web site and TheDieselPage.com's BB forum.
As an example, cookies can be used to retain your username and password as required by the TheDieselPage.com's BB forum and member/subscriber web pages, so you don't have to re-enter user/login codes each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, or personally identifiable information. Accessing member areas of our bulletin board forum require cookies.
However, you can choose to refuse our cookies, delete our cookie from your hard drive, or turn off the TheDieselPage.com forum cookie at any time by updating your forum profile preferences.
Purchasing and/or Credit Card Information:
TheDieselPage.com strives to maintain strict security for your private information. Our online membership & book ordering form all employ the use of PayPal for credit card transactions, to become a subscribing member, renew your membership or to order any of the printed and bound books we offer. PayPal was chosen to handle all credit card transactions because of their vast resources available to provide world-class security
for any online transaction.
Technical Support:
Any personal information you provide to us in the course of obtaining technical support, or asking other questions about TheDieselPage.com will be used only for the purpose for which it was submitted. We may store the information, but we will not use it for any other purpose or disclose it to any third parties without your permission. Technical questions pertaining to maintenance or repair of any diesel light-truck could appear in a future TheDieselPage.com web page, published article or in a future Question & Answer technical page. If you have any objection to having your name or e-mail address disclosed in this manner, please let us know at the time the question is asked. Only your name and e-mail address could be disclosed in this manner.
Use and Disclosure of Your Information:
TheDieselPage.com uses the personal information it collects from forms you fill out on our site or in our forum/mailing list registrations to:
Allow users to access and use our content and services.
Supply users with instructions necessary to access information, and technical resources.
Provide users of content and services on our site with information about special offers and promotions; and
Improve our content and services by using statistical analysis and evaluation of user data.
We use the anonymous information we collect from the other methods described above, such as cookie information, to develop demographic information concerning user trends, count the number of users of our content and services, to provide advertising services and to improve our online content and editorial services.
Except as noted above, we do not and will not disclose your private, personally identifiable information to any third party for any purpose without your prior consent. The Diesel Page has always been guided by the values expressed in the "Golden Rule" (Matthew 7:12), where we treat others how we ourselves wish to be treated. However, TheDieselPage.com reserves the right to disclose your personal information if
such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to legal claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, its employees, members, customers, or the public. All reasonable care is taken by our staff in handling your personal information to ensure its security, both offline and online.
TheDieselPage.com
What's New: | Feature Articles: | Product Reviews: | Member's Area:
Join Us: | Duramax Diesel Page: | Advertisers: | Classified Ads: | Books:
Send e-mail to: turbo@TheDieselPage.com
Copyright © by The Diesel Page
www.TheDieselPage.com
